{
    "id": "64484934149e46458b3dc9f2c9ce8dbc",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I will be staying here for ……………………… more days.",
            "description": "A few indicates a small number.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "the few"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is junior …………………………… me.",
            "description": "The words junior and senior are followed by to.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "China is ………………………… than India.",
            "description": "Use a comparative expression before than.",
            "answers": [
                "larger",
                "the larger",
                "the largest"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ………………………….. than her.",
            "description": "Younger is the comparative form of young. ",
            "answers": [
                "younger",
                "the younger",
                "more young"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I gave the kitten …………………………… milk.",
            "description": "Use little with uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "a little",
                "a few",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Of the two routes, this is ………………………………",
            "description": "Use the comparative form when a group consists of just two people or things. ",
            "answers": [
                "short",
                "the shorter",
                "the shortest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We got ……………………………….. rain this year. The crops are all dying.",
            "description": "Little means hardly any.",
            "answers": [
                "a little",
                "little",
                "the little"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This material is superior ………………………….. that.",
            "description": "Use to after superior and inferior. ",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "than",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ……………………………… of the four men.",
            "description": "The superlative is used to compare a person or thing with the group to which they/it belong(s).",
            "answers": [
                "the older",
                "oldest",
                "the oldest"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I do not earn as much as …………………………… does.",
            "description": "The subject form is used before a verb.",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A dog is ……………………………… than a cat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more intelligent",
                "the more intelligent",
                "the most intelligent"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Hindi ………………………….. in many parts of India.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is speaking",
                "spoken",
                "is spoken"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}